We're here today
with Cho Yeo-jeong and Ha Seok-jin.
Not only is Seok-jin a great actor,
but he's known
as one of the smartest actors out there.
Hanyang University's engineering major,
an intellectual heartthrob, so to say.
-Intellectual heartthrob.
-Yes.
Also, he was the winner
of The Devil's Plan,
a strategy-driven survival game show.
-He has receipts.
-I remember.
-One of our chefs studied engineering too.
-Is that so?
A guy who studied
at Rose-Hulman Institute of Technology.
WE KNOW THAT GUY
Who could it be?
"Rose-Hulman."
-It's probably Chef Jong-won.
-Jong-won?
-He studied engineering in the States.
-Jong-won.
I didn't graduate, though. I dropped out.
You switched to culinary arts.
I'm sure you had a particular major.
I majored in civil engineering
and optical engineering.
You must've studied mechanics.
I DID
-It deals with streets and bridges.
-What about you, Seok-jin?
-I majored in mechanical engineering.
-Mechanical engineering.
We probably studied
a few similar subjects.
HOW COOL
-I also attended a vo-tech school.
-Good for you.
Vo-tech school?
JUNG-HWAN WANTED TO JOIN THEM
I didn't think
you'd suddenly chime in like that.
We probably studied
a few of the same subjects.
He went to a vo-tech high
but majored in business at college.
INTERDISCIPLINARY TALENT
I studied architecture in high school.
BLUSHING A BIT
Did you study mechanics too?
You didn't pick up skills there, did you?
I often used triangle rulers too.
LIKE THIS
-The angle's important.
-I always had to.
That's all I ever did
while learning about architecture.
Your family could've hoped
you'd make use of your major
-and gotten a job instead.
-Yes, instead of getting into acting.
I had a chance
to dip a toe into the industry,
so my family told me to try it for a year,
see if I like doing that job, and if not,
I could always go back to studying.
My agency built on the momentum
after my debut
and suggested that I continue
instead of returning to school.
You two are similar in that
while you were in college,
-you decided to change courses.
-They did.
And one of them is a real chef,
-and the other one will play one.
-Exactly.
Mechanical engineering
and civil engineering.
And me, architecture.
THE FORMER STRIKER
FINDS HIS CHANCE TO SLIDE IN
I don't get me either.
EXCELLENT, THAT WAS SMOOTH
But I guess there's this thing.
People who study this field
-like to fiddle with tools.
-So true.
We learn to use tools easily
and tend to fix broken things quickly too.
When kitchen tools break at work,
I tell my staff
not to send it anywhere for repairs
because I do it myself.
So you're really like that?
They have that kind of pride.
-So I've thrown out a number of tools.
-Right.
-I always send it out to have it fixed.
-Always?
You'll be playing a chef
on your upcoming project.
And chefs come
in many different characters.
Some are attentive, some can be snippy.
He's overall quite attentive,
but he can be quite snippy in the kitchen.
A level-headed character.
I want to observe the chefs today
and pick up what I can.
-Then I had a question.
-What is it?
Chef Sam
always has a smile on his face
and is so warm-hearted.
So does a guy like him
also change in the kitchen,
become difficult,
and even swear when he works?
Yes, I'm very difficult.
He changes completely. Look at his canine.
I hear he bites people.
-Give us an example.
-What are you like when you're mad?
-He may have to act angry in the kitchen.
-I had a scene, actually.
The fridge broke down
and the ingredients all got spoiled,
but none of my staff members caught on.
-So I had to go and berate them.
-They must be reprimanded.
But the level of anger I should express
was solely based on my interpretation.
-I had lots of room, so I began to think.
-That's something…
-…that'll make you completely lose it.
-Completely?
FOCUSED
It's about management.
I'd go, "How come no one knew about this?"
-It can't be like that. That's not anger.
-That's not getting angry.
HESITANT
I get really furious
when something like that happens.
Yes, so how?
-Don't just explain it.
-It's like this.
I gather all of them and go,
"How come no one knew?"
-So you berate them.
-No.
Don't smile and do it
like you're actually there.
Just be yourself and go…
OH, YOU ENDEARING GUY
YOU CUTE LITTLE THING, HUH?
COMING LIVE FROM THE SCENE
NOW, THAT'S WHAT HE NEEDS TO DO
If you ever get mad in the kitchen,
please take a video and show us.
I'll study him through the CCTV footage.
Chefs, do you have any tips for him
to portray a chef more realistically?
In my case, I often use tools like scales,
like precision scales and rulers.
As an engineering major.
But in the kitchen,
-I think Nam-no is on the active side.
-Yes.
His actions are big, making him look cool.
Any tips, Chef Nam-no?
Well, actually…
CHEWING…
-Stop eating the gummies.
-How many gummies have you had?
-You're still munching on those?
-It's been hours.
He finished almost everything.
NO ATE THE PILE OF GUMMIES
When you look at ingredients
like onions and carrots,
don't look at them like this.
If you're to act it out,
you must glare upward like this
and give them a serious look.
That's the secret?
Don't we call that wild-eyed?
Like this.
NOW, LOOK!
SERIOUS LOOK
OBSERVING SERIOUSLY
It looks like he's picking a fight.
And throw a raw piece
in your mouth for no reason.
THAT WAS AN EXCUSE TO EAT ANOTHER GUMMY…
EUREKA
It's to check.
TRIES IT RIGHT AWAY
-Glare up at it.
-Glare up.
He's looking weird because of you.
COPYING YOON NAM-NO
LET ME TRY!
-It turned into a comedy piece.
-Wait.
-Did you say you wanted to meet Eun-yeong?
-You said that?
I watched the show and noticed
that unlike when I was last on the show,
-people began to dance a lot.
-You're right.
But the moment she began to dance,
she owned the studio.
THE BEGINNING OF HER MAD EYES ERA
-Her eyes suddenly shifted drastically.
-And it's just her.
So I wanted to use that
for my performance.
What kind of signal must I give
to my brains to show those eyes?
-I began to study her…
-He took it as art.
…but I couldn't copy it.
It's something you'd call
split personality,
playing two characters at once.
NOTICES HER
Why are you laughing so hard?
I'm also an actor,
so I had a similar thought.
"I should copy her."
-Copy her?
-What's going on, Eun-yeong?
So she has a knack for acting?
What's the process
that's going on in your head?
You become one with it
and just accept it.
-Accept who?
-From what I've seen,
it's not that
she puts in a certain neural signal.
She has to sever something in her brain.
A neurectomy.
UNDERSTOOD
Eun-yeong, did you
also want to meet Seok-jin?
Yes, my husband is known
to be his lookalike.
DISAPPROVES
I've seen lots of articles pop up,
and of course, I became curious.
I looked him up to see
how similar we looked
but I couldn't find a picture of his face.
Right. He's not a public figure.
I hear he goes around wearing a mask
after hearing that he looks like him.
REALLY?
He said he felt embarrassed
to go around without a mask,
because people may go,
"Let's see if he looks like Ha Seok-jin."
That's why he wears a mask.
He looks like a gentler version of him.
But the vibes they give off seem similar.
THEY LOOK SIMILAR IN HER EYES
I was at her wedding,
so why didn't I pick up on that vibe?
-I see.
-Right?
Nam-no, did you pick it up?
No.
-He must've been busy eating.
-He never stopped.
Maybe it was Jee Seok-jin.
-Jee Seok-jin?
-He's handsome.
He said he looked like Jee Seok-jin.
WHY ARE YOU BRINGING HIM UP?
He's good-looking.
I can't do the show with him.
He's so annoying.
Her husband is good-looking, though.
And so is Jee Seok-jin.
-All right.
-That went pretty far.
-Doesn't he, though?
-Seriously. Not at all.
I can't tell by this picture.
-I kind of get it.
-You get it, right?
-I get what you mean.
-It's his hairstyle.
-No.
-But honestly, no, not at all.
-I'm serious.
-It's this part.
-Yes, this part.
-And the dimples.
This is the second time having
Seok-jin on Chef & My Fridge.
-It's been 11 years since his last visit.
-Hello, I'm Ha Seok-jin.
Since the last time I was here,
I've aged quite a bit
so my taste in food changed too.
When I'd go on dates,
I used to stick with Western cuisine,
such as pasta and whatnot.
But these days,
I prefer eobok-jaengban, hot pot platter.
Or baeksuk with shingled
hedgehog mushrooms.
-I'm craving shingled hedgehogs.
-Your appetite changed a lot.
I think I'm in the process
of becoming an ajae, an old dude.
I hear you talk to yourself often,
-Seok-jin.
-Really?
-That's what old dudes do.
-Only old guys do that.
I find myself mumbling.
"What's in the fridge?"
-I find myself adding melodies too.
-It happens.
Even as I drive, I go,
"The traffic is heavy."
-Yes, you're right.
-I keep finding myself doing that.
I often chat with my GPS navigator.
It goes, "Turn left."
I go, "Gotta turn left. Gotcha."
-Yes, we do talk to ourselves a lot.
-My gosh.
Jong-won, are there moments when you go,
"Have I become an old dude?"
I work with lots of Gen MZ people, right?
When I make a joke,
at times, you hear people laughing,
and you can tell that it was genuine.
But at other times, it's faked.
FORCED LAUGHTER
I keep hearing laughs like these.
-"You're so funny."
-"How funny."
"Really?"
I don't think
it's that kind of a dad joke.
They call my jokes dad jokes
because they go,
"Oh, there's the dead joke again."
COLD SILENCE
HAHAHAHA
(GUYS, JUST LAUGH FOR NOW)
-He's funny.
-I'm laughing because he's the head chef.
WE CAN'T HELP BUT APPLAUD, CHEF
I do it to lighten up the mood.
He's so funny.
He doesn't give a darn.
-Once you get older, you really don't.
-Now that you mention it,
once I've become older,
I find myself standing on the balcony,
staring at the scenery.
POV: A WEEKEND MORNING FOR DADS
I stare out for ages
with hands clasped to the back.
-It happens.
-I didn't do that when I was younger.
THE GRANDPA CAN RELATE
Sung-jun, you're yet to feel old, right?
The thing is, legally speaking,
people born in 1995 are still YCC.
So I'm not really sure.
So ask Nam-no, who's now an OCC.
What now? Young…
-What's that?
-What now?
-YCC?
-What's YCC?
I also recently found out
from my kitchen staff.
I saw them
chatting happily with one another,
and they go,
"You're too OCC to know, right?"
-You wouldn't know.
-OCC? Too old?
-Exactly.
-So there are YCC and OCC,
but I was too embarrassed to ask.
-It's a recent meme.
-YCC, OCC.
OCC, YCC.
Yeo-jeong was greatly shocked to find out
that Sung-jun was born in 1995.
I wasn't surprised.
Not at all.
-She's acting.
-I'm YCC. YoungCreatorCrew.
Sure, YCC.
Born in 1995. It's fascinating.
Seok-jin is really into Japanese ramen,
so he goes around trying different places.
If I were into pasta or Chinese food,
I would've needed a group to go with.
But all I need to order
is a single bowl for ramen,
-so it's easier to go alone.
-Right.
I'm sure you have a list of good places.
I always take a picture
of the bowl whenever I eat,
and at times,
even a video to show the soup's texture.
If you see a photo, do you recall
where you had it and what it was like?
I probably remember most places
I've visited in the last two, three years.
That's how
an intellectual heartthrob works.
We asked him beforehand
and received some photos
from Seok-jin.
Let's see how many places he has been to.
That's a lot.
-This is all ramen.
-Yes.
That's a lot.
An awful lot.
Did you eat some of them overseas?
They're mostly domestic.
Maybe a few places in Japan.
There are that many ramen places in Seoul?
There are lots.
I go to lots of places too.
Really?
Let's pick out a place and see…
-If he remembers.
-…if he remembers.
We'll pick out something randomly.
Why don't we go up to the screen
and point at one?
That's so analog.
-Then they'll enlarge it.
-Do it, vo-tech high kid.
I'll pick one at random.
-Let the architecture major go.
-The vo-tech high kid.
-"Let the architecture major go"?
-Yes.
-This one looks unique.
-I can't see.
Yes, that's new.
The meat is hanged on the edge.
-Yes, over the edge.
-Right?
I think that's from
K restaurant in Nonhyeon-dong.
They did that with their ramen.
-He really remembers.
-Probably.
The one to the right of that
is from Eunpyeong-gu,
M restaurant.
-This one is Eunpyeong-gu?
-Yes.
The one on the right of that
is H place in Yeonnam-dong.
They give you all this roasted seaweed?
Yes, I like to add extra.
-I see.
-It was extra.
Like a nobleman's hat.
THE LAUGHTER OF PEOPLE ACTUALLY LAUGHING
Can only nobles have it?
That's W place near Gangnam Station.
-So it's mostly like that.
-He remembers everything.
How does he remember all that?
He's an intellectual heartthrob
and a ramen heartthrob.
And now, we're about to open
Seok-jin's fridge again after 11 years.
Back then, I remember
-that he was really into beer.
-Homebrewed.
-Yes, he brewed it at home or something.
-Yes.
Do you still do that?
No, I don't make anything anymore.
-It's vain.
-It's all in vain.
You have that kind of passion
when you're younger.
I'm kind of scared
because when they took that fridge,
I was on set, not home.
I should've been there
and told them to leave some stuff.
But you couldn't.
So literally everything is here.
-This is exciting.
-It's pretty much empty.
-It's the naked truth.
-It's like showing my underwear drawer.
-That's nice.
-And we love that.
We love a good search and seizure.
-We love it when the homeowner isn't home.
-Exactly.
We never misrepresent
what it actually looked like.
Everything is exactly as it was.
-It needs some misrepresentation.
-Oh, gosh.
It's been 11 years.
It's nice to see his fridge again.
-We present Seok-jin's fridge!
-Fridge!
-Whoa.
-He has lots of stuff.
-We present Seok-jin's fridge!
-Fridge!
LOOKING NEAT, UNLIKE HOW HE WAS WORRIED
It looks neat.
As expected, some delivery food.
The first two shelves
are mostly delivery food.
Did you have the entire fridge delivered?
Let's see what he likes to order.
-That's so relatable.
-Are these all ramen?
-Kimchi-jjigae.
That's a lot left over.
I divide it into portions
and warm it up in a smaller bowl.
What's this one?
-It's milky broth.
-Is it dwaeji-gukbap?
Either dwaeji-gukbap or seolleong-tang.
-It looks untouched.
-I haven't even opened it.
I had to order some more
to reach the minimum amount.
-For later.
-So I ordered another soup.
-Tacos?
-Tacos.
At times, I like to do
a collaboration of different cuisines.
-A collaboration?
-A mix-and-match.
-A fusion meal.
It's fun to eliminate those leftovers
like you're playing Tetris.
I heard about a "Ha Seok-jin set"
in Chinese restaurants.
-Ha Seok-jin set?
-What?
-A while ago…
-How often did you have it?
There are jjajangmyeon types
that serve the sauce on the side, right?
And if you order jjamppong rice,
you get lots of soup with it.
So I'd split it up into three portions,
-and the jjajang sauce is a lot too.
-Right.
So first, I eat the soup and the rice,
then the soup and the noodles,
and with the sauce next time.
It's probably the way I split up
two bowls into different meals.
SHARING HIS FORMULA
His engineering brain is at work.
I've always liked to mix up my meals.
Now, the second shelf.
-These must've been delivered too.
-Yes, the sides.
I see some kimchi and pickles.
You're thrifty.
-Look at this stash.
-Probably Tabasco packets.
-I like to keep them too.
-It's a shame to throw them out.
-I don't want to throw them out.
-Yes, I have a stash too.
What's this? What's this powder?
That one?
I had mountains of Parmesan
after ordering pizza,
-so I gathered them.
-A great idea.
Did you rip out those packets?
Yes, and it's pretty full now.
I like how thrifty you are
in saving all this food,
but do you eat it all?
I always make sure I pull out
-ones I had delivered first.
-Right.
First-in, first-out.
You remember the order?
BRAIN LOGICS
The ones that arrive early go to the back
like drinks at a convenience store,
so I pull out the ones that arrived first.
You know which ones you ordered earlier,
so you eat the older ones first.
THE FRIDGE IS IN MY HEAD
I find these things intriguing.
It's like a typical home.
You brought all those?
-I should've stopped you.
-Oh, no.
This isn't a lid.
-That's a first.
-That's too realistic.
-That's a dish.
-That's actually candid.
SMH
-What's in here?
-Let's see it.
This is a bowl
Seok-jin left covered with a dish.
Here it is.
-What's that?
-Soup?
It looks like broth.
That's…
-Jeez.
-What is it?
WHAT IS IT?
I made suyuk, boiled meat.
I had some broth left
after making the dish,
and the broth smelled so good,
although it tasted a bit strong.
So I had it chilled
to mix it with something later.
I should've thrown it out.
There's one more.
-Is this a saucer?
-A saucer?
-It's a saucer for a teacup.
-You're right.
-My mom used to do that.
-This was a regular dish.
What's in here?
Ta-da.
-Lard?
-It's this.
-It's beef fat.
-Beef fat.
-You have beef fat?
-Beef fat?
-Why is it red?
-Oh, well,
when I left soup in the fridge
after it got delivered,
the oil rose and hardened.
-That layer.
-It's a mix of chili oil and beef fat.
I usually ate it
after skimming the fat off,
then I came to think,
"Maybe I can use this oil."
He has that research spirit.
You have that scientist side.
Let's go to the bins on the side.
NERVOUS
-What's this?
-Wait.
It looks as if he's getting interrogated.
-Blueberry jam?
-No.
-There's something else inside.
-It's something else?
-How thrifty.
-It says blueberry jam.
-What's that?
-It's probably some onion thing.
-Onion?
-It smells like onion.
-It's been a while. Look.
-At least three years, I say.
Wait a second.
There can't be just one of these.
What's this? Gosh. What is it?
This expired
in 2017?!
In 2017?
He should've had it before March 9, 2017.
MIND-BOGGLING
I get it's canned, but…
It's probably pâté.
-Pâté.
I'll hold onto it for nine more months
and throw it out after a decade.
What's this one?
-What's that?
-It's new.
Whoa, there's a life-form inside.
-Life-form?
-There's a life-form?
-See? There's a life-form moving inside.
-It's moving?
I've seen something like this
in a science lab.
It's yeoneo-jang, spicy marinated salmon.
-Yeoneo-jang?
Made on February 5th, 2021.
Best by seven days
after the production date.
OH MY GOODNESS
You should've had it within seven days.
Seven days?
You'll have to throw this out.
-I don't want you to open it.
-What?
BUT I'M SO CURIOUS♥
BUT WE
REALLY AREN'T
-Sung-ju.
-Yes?
Can you open it in your seat?
But Yeo-jeong is there.
PROTECT YEO-JEONG AT ALL COST
The rule of the show is that
whoever opens it has a bite.
Yes.
That's our ironclad rule.
-Try the sauce.
-Let's check its condition.
-We all told you not to open it.
-It's new.
Why would you open it?
It's going to blow up.
-Be careful.
-Look at that color.
-I'm scared.
-Why do I feel itchy?
I'm scared.
Whoa, the gas.
Hide me.
The gas.
It's open.
SAFE
It'd be jeotgal by now.
It turned gray.
-The salmon.
-That's scary.
These are salmon slices.
So Seok-jin had this side?
-You don't throw things out.
-Is it thriftiness?
I never really go through my fridge.
-And throw this out.
-Everything should go.
-This is going.
-And this one.
Hey, check those too.
This was good by November 4th, 2022.
June 18th, 2023.
Let's get rid of this bin.
They were exiled.
We'll throw these out.
I didn't know it expired
and had it once a few months ago.
-What?
-This?
But I didn't get sick.
I did throw it out after.
Are you asking us not to throw these out?
No, please do.
I'm not sure if you want us to or not.
-We must do it for his sake.
-We can't let him get sick.
My immunity level
slowly seems to be rising.
Do you enjoy drinking alone?
This is makgeolli, right?
-And sake.
-This must be sake.
Do you enjoy sake and makgeolli?
Whenever I have to shoot
for a long time on set and variety shows,
I'm in a state of hyperarousal,
and they help me calm down.
It's my after-work drink.
He'll need a lot today.
-To the freezer, then?
-Let's look at the freezer.
He has lots of stuff.
-Sea urchin roe.
-He has sea urchin roe?
Those are fresh as h…
I almost said "heck."
WATCH OUT FOR HYPERAROUSAL
I recently appeared on
another variety show
and had sea urchin roe pasta.
That sounds great.
-You have bread in the freezer.
-Bread.
My younger sister lives in Germany,
so she sent it to me,
saying it's popular there.
I left it in the freezer,
and it's been about a month.
I still don't get
why people love plain bread.
-Sounds good.
-What type of bread do you like?
I like the ones that kids like.
Things like pizza bread
or sausage bread.
-Or red bean bread.
-Red bean bread.
I love red bean paste.
Red bean bread isn't for kids.
It's for old dudes.
A-HA!
-So you did cook before.
-He has dried seafood.
These are dried seafood for broth.
Anchovies and Dokdo shrimp.
When I order tsukemen,
a type of dipping ramen,
I like to eat it
with some powdered seafood.
-It adds lots of flavors.
-It must be savory.
You have lots of meat.
Why do you have so much?
-Pork belly.
-For bulgogi. Whoa.
-Beef brisket.
-Right.
You must love meat.
I got those as presents
and they're great quality.
But I usually go out to Majang-dong
with my friends and eat meat there.
So those are some leftovers
because I couldn't eat them alone,
but they're good meat.
It felt awkward
to grill the meat alone at home.
What's the problem
with grilling it at home?
I used to do it from time to time.
But about two or three years ago,
I looked up how to cook good meat
on the day of a major holiday.
So I heated up a pan
to sear the meat front and back.
Then the alarm went off
in the entire building.
Because of the smoke?
-The alarm?
-So the security guard came
and banged on my door,
asking if I was okay.
I caused a nuisance to my entire building
on a holiday.
It was embarrassing.
I was kind of traumatized by the event,
so I stopped grilling meat alone at home.
-That's an unfortunate memory.
-It is.
So he rarely grills meat at home.
You could've gone to your parents' place.
Why were you alone on a holiday?
I usually stop by the day before.
They'll start nagging
if I stay for too long.
-Nagging.
-I return quickly.
-Of course.
-Urging him to marry soon.
Yes, that happens.
Let's see the shelf-stable ingredients.
They brought all that? Whoa.
What are these noodles?
It's probably instant ramen
packaged like that.
-You don't know what many of these are.
-No.
-Some of them are from my fans.
-Gifts from fans.
I'm curious about a few of those,
so I wanted to ask the chefs
to use them today.
-What is it?
-There's something
similar to vinegar somewhere.
It's balsamic vinegar.
I got it as a present
and have never used it.
-It looks good.
-That's a good one.
Can I have it?
GIGGLING
-It'll taste good in a dish.
-Give it to me.
I LOVE VINEGAR♥
That soy sauce back there
is something I got
while traveling in Japan
after hearing it was famous.
It was really good,
so I want to eat something
-that uses that soy sauce.
-Sure.
-All these.
-These.
-Please make use of these.
That's all for Seok-jin's fridge.
FINISHED CHECKING OUT SEOK-JIN'S FRIDGE
I wonder what he's looking to eat today.
Here are his orders. Show us.
-Grown Man's Soup.
PLEASED
The old dude's soup.
I get it already.
-Gosh.
-That soup.
Man.
Something hearty.
WHAT'S ALL THIS SOUND?
I want to eat a soup dish
that makes me make those noises,
made by professional chefs.
Soup dish.
Grown Man's Soup.
What's the second order?
-What's next? Problematic Meat.
-Problematic Meat.
He has lots of meat. That's why.
They're good meat.
Both the beef and the pork
come in a variety of cuts too.
I've never been able to use them,
so I'd like to eat it
in a deliciously prepared dish.
The four remaining chefs are Hyun-suk,
Sam, Eun-yeong, and Sung-jun.
I'll go
for Grown Man's Soup.
-The soup?
-I like to eat like an old dude too, and…
-And you have a beard.
-She's really bad.
Yes, a beard.
If you look closely, I have hair
on my chin. I'm an actual old dude.
SUDDEN CONFESSION OF FACIAL HAIR
-Seok-jin… Yes, you're right.
-It grew out already.
You can see it by the evening.
WHAT?
She means facial hair.
I didn't know what she meant.
FACEPALM
After I shared this,
someone sent me a shaver as a present.
PROTECT THE GODDESS OF CHINESE CUISINE
FROM THE FANS
-I'm serious.
-You can't show it on TV.
-I really got it as a present.
-The high beams.
Anyway, I want to make
a delicious Chinese dish.
-Of course.
-I'll make soup.
ALL RIGHT
So Eun-yeong is in.
We need someone older
to make that soup dish.
-Hyun-suk.
-Hyun-suk should join for the grown man.
I'll go.
-Hyun-suk.
-I was going to go.
-I have lots of ramen places pinned.
-He loves ramen too.
I also love ramen so much,
and I recommend great places
-to my fellow chefs.
-He does.
-He loves ramen.
-So I want to make him
a bowl of ramen
that a grown man would love.
Excuse me.
The order isn't Grown Man's Tears.
It's not tears, but soup.
-It's so good that it'll make him cry.
-So delicious.
Eun-yeong and Hyun-suk
are up against each other.
-Then it's decided. Problematic Meat.
-Problematic Meat.
-Sam versus Sung-jun.
-Sung-jun.
Then let us begin the soup dish round
between Eun-yeong and Hyun-suk!
Let us begin the first round of cook-off
with Seok-jin's ingredients.
The one who recently got
a shaver as a present,
the self-proclaimed biggest old dude,
Chef Park Eun-yeong,
versus the actual oldest dude
of the show, Chef Choi Hyun-suk.
Did you shave your face? It looks clean.
Some time has passed already,
so I should go and shave again
around 6 to 7 p.m.
-But you did it in the morning.
-I did.
-And again at 7 p.m.
-Twice a day?
She'd throw anything out there
if it could help her win stars.
-I go feral for the stars.
-What now?
I go feral for the stars.
HOW CUTE
Her charm is that you can never hate her.
SMILE
-Look at her face.
-She's bubbly.
It looks like
something else is on her mind.
No one can read her face.
Eun-yeong, do you believe
it's disadvantageous for Hyun-suk?
Yes, it's because
the order is Grown Man's Soup.
Chef Hyun-suk isn't a grown man,
but an aged man.
He doesn't suit the topic.
He hears something like this,
but he still laughs it off.
-What if it were me?
-It would've been awful.
He'd wushu me right away.
-You tend to favor her.
-He does.
I wouldn't call it that.
-Is it because he has a daughter?
-Well…
She always tries hard
-and stays bubbly in her demeanor.
-Yes.
I think that's great,
so I want to show support.
-I do the same.
-Is Sung-jun different?
-He tries hard too.
-He always does his best.
And I'm bubbly too.
Turning on the emergency light
at the right time is not an easy job.
You're right.
-He plays a big part.
-He's in charge of the "emergency" meme.
Well, everyone tries hard.
He'll do well on his own.
MEANING: HE DOESN'T NEED ME
He just doesn't like him.
-What do you mean?
-You're on your own.
She also said something like this.
"Hyun-suk isn't exactly a ggondae,
a nosy boomer."
-What do you mean?
-He's not a ggondae?
In my opinion,
for someone to be a ggondae,
they'll have to be nosy.
-But he doesn't care about anyone else.
-Right.
So he's not a ggondae.
IS IT A COMPLIMENT OR WHAT?
I share my MBTI type with him weekly,
and he forgets every time.
And he's surprised each time?
Every single time.
He always goes, "The same as me?"
He only cares about his business.
-That's hilarious.
-So what's Sung-jun's MBTI type?
His MBTI type is
ENTJ.
-We just said it was the same as his.
-I told him today.
I shared it with him today,
and he tends to dislike
people who are like him.
He definitely does.
-Like he's looking in a mirror.
-It should be his therapy.
We tend to dislike
those who are the most like us.
CLENCHING TEETH…
That's why he's my master.
CHEF EUN-YEONG'S INGREDIENTS:
DRIED DOKDO SHRIMP, HEADLESS DRIED SHRIMP
COCKTAIL SHRIMP, TILEFISH,
KNIFE-CUT NOODLES, AND MORE
First up, Chef Eun-yeong.
What are you making?
In order to attack the aged man,
Hyun-suk the OCC, OldCreatorCrew,
I prepared a dish called
OldSoupSoup.
OldSoupSoup?
-OldSoupSoup.
-OldSoupSoup. Not OCC. OSS.
-I see.
It's an attack on Hyun-suk.
I'm going to make
Hong Kong-style shrimp noodle soup.
Shrimp noodle soup
is usually made with fresh shrimp,
but he didn't have any.
So I'll use dried shrimp for the broth,
and I'll also add shrimp that'll seem
freshly caught, although they weren't.
-With frozen shrimp?
-I'll make the noodle soup
that he'll love and start chugging on.
That's what I've prepared.
-All right. That sounds good.
-It sounds so good.
CHEF HYUN-SUK'S INGREDIENTS:
DRIED DOKDO SHRIMP, HEADLESS DRIED SHRIMP
PORK BELLY, SCALLION, KELP SEASONING,
SOY SAUCE, BEEF BONE BROTH
The name of my dish is
Don't Shrimp Me
Because I'm Old.
A chef never ages.
He merely gets more ripe with experience.
-Overcooked.
-Completely cooked.
He's like well-aged kimchi.
-Way past cooked.
-Well-done.
He's glaring at you.
-He glares at you when you talk.
-Why do you do that?
-He always glares at you.
-My favorite ramen joint
is a place in Hokkaido
famous for shrimp ramen.
You have to wait an hour and a half
even at midnight.
And when you're nearby, the air smells
like broth made with 100,000 shrimps.
It's my all-time favorite ramen,
and it's extremely rich and savory.
So I'd like to make
this heavily flavored ramen
that old men can truly enjoy
after facing years of hardships.
The restaurant he mentioned
has such a long line
-that I had given up.
-It's great.
-It's that long?
-It's so long.
-I haven't had it either.
-And you can try that today.
It's really famous.
-It's a shrimp round.
-Yes.
Will you make the noodles?
I'm making fresh noodles.
WILL MAKE FRESH NOODLES
And now, let us begin the round
"Grown Man's Soup."
David and Goliath.
She married solely for this round.
She's determined to win a star
from her husband's lookalike,
Chef Park Eun-yeong.
He had aged solely for this round.
-Our oldest OldCreatorCrew,
-OCC!
…Chef Choi Hyun-suk.
Who will capture the heart
of the grown man, Ha Seok-jin?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
It's a soup dish round.
A SOUP DISH ROUND!
He's toasting the shrimp.
He starts by toasting the shrimp.
HEADLESS DRIED SHRIMP
Is it better to boil the broth
after toasting them?
This brings out more flavor.
YOU!
TINY SHAKES
-That's mantecare. "I'll do what you do."
-I don't do it like that.
AN HOMAGE TO HIS OTHER SELF
He toasts the shrimp
to use them as the broth.
Whoa. Japanese kelp seasoning.
He threw in kelp seasoning and pork belly.
You're adding kelp into the soup?
-With pork.
-Is it… What's that?
-What did you squeeze in?
-Ginger?
-Garlic?
-Ginger.
Talk to us while you cook.
What did you squeeze in?
Hey, OCC!
-Chef OCC!
-He can't hear you.
THE INGREDIENT DETECTOR IS ON IT
SNIFF
-It's ginger.
-Ginger.
I see. Thank you, Ho-young.
WHAT'S EUN-YEONG'S FIRST STEP?
She starts with garlic.
ONE SHOT, ONE KILL
PREPS THE INGREDIENTS FIRST!
1. PREP GARLIC, GREEN ONION, AND TOMATOES
FINISHED PREPPING, AND…
As expected,
she's toasting the shrimp too.
-You're right.
-She added tomatoes too.
With tomatoes?
STORE-BOUGHT VEGGIE BROTH
I somehow thought
she'd make meat-based broth.
-Spicy.
-What's that you just added?
-Red pepper powder.
-A bit of red pepper powder.
-Tomatoes, dried shrimp…
-Hong Kong-style.
2 EGGS
Is he cooking eggs?
WHAT ABOUT THE TOASTED SHRIMP?
Shrimp is the key ingredient for both.
INTO THE BONE BROTH!
It'll have so much umami.
-What?
-Ramyeon noodles?
-Ramyeon?
-To make it thicker.
To add starch.
-He wants to make it thicker.
-By adding starch.
-I see.
-He's making it richer.
The soup tastes much deeper
once you cook it with oil-fried noodles.
And it adds richness.
But the noodles will get soggy.
He won't use it.
-Just the starchiness.
-It's a great idea.
WHAT'S NEXT?
He's using that soy sauce too.
He's adding soy sauce and cooking wine.
I think he'll marinate
the boiled egg in the sauce.
Eun-yeong uses tilefish.
PREPPING THE FISH!
3. SLICE TILEFISH FILLETS
Is that for the shrimp soup?
I'm making fish balls.
Fish balls. You're Meatball Queen.
He didn't have fresh shrimp.
FISH BALLS FOR THE SHRIMP NOODLE SOUP!
Are you only using the meat?
Yes, just the meat.
TILEFISH MEAT
I guess she'll grind it.
-Yes.
-She'll grind it to make fish balls.
-She's making fish balls right now.
-She's only using egg whites.
Why do you only use egg whites?
If you use whole eggs,
the yolk creates a dull, sticky flavor.
So I'm using just the egg whites as glue.
She's making fish balls with tilefish.
SESAME OIL
-You need fish balls for the noodle soup.
-Of course.
It adds a nice touch.
The fish balls. The meatball queen.
She's making fish balls.
-Fish balls.
She made one already.
She's very fast.
"Boing."
-Fish balls.
-Like shrimp balls.
-"Boing."
-She made it so easily.
FISH BALLS ARE MADE INSTANTLY
FLOUR
2. MAKE NOODLE DOUGH
BY MIXING FLOUR AND WATER
The dough.
It looks a bit too thin.
QUICKLY ADDS MORE FLOUR
Trouble with the noodles.
-There's trouble?
-It's not working?
GRINDS AGAIN
Let's see if it turned out okay.
It looks good. Nice dough.
DO NOT WORRY!
OLDCREATORCREW!
SHIELDING WITH HIS WHOLE BODY
OH, BOY
For ramen.
He's making the noodles.
First, flatten the dough.
One more time.
Jong-won isn't allowed to help.
GIGGLE
-We have to see it.
-There was a controversy.
It's nice that Jong-won is helping,
but his head is blocking the view.
A CONTROVERSY OVER THE CAMERA BLOCK
WHAT ABOUT THIS TIME?
It looks like his noodles
have turned out thin and nice.
SMOOTH
That's Hyun-suk.
It's taking him a while.
SNICKERING…
You're about five minutes in.
THAT PUNK…
THE DOUGH IS READY
So funny.
WHAT'S EUN-YEONG UP TO?
Was it just egg whites? Or starch too?
I added a bit of starch too.
She made that with tilefish, right?
-Tilefish?
-I did.
STICK THE TAIL ON
AND THE HEAD
A SHRIMP-SHAPED FISH BALL
He didn't have fresh shrimp,
so I wanted to give him fish balls.
Fish balls.
He's making the ramen noodles now.
He's making the noodles now.
It's coming out.
In tagliatelle size.
COMES OUT SMOOTHLY
-They're thick.
-We can see it now.
He just made fresh noodles.
Aren't they a bit too thick?
-They look thick.
-They're pretty thick for ramen.
-Right?
-How unique.
It looks like kal-guksu noodles.
In that case, shouldn't you have asked him
his preferred thickness of the noodles?
-Yes.
-Right?
Do you prefer
thin noodles or thick noodles?
I actually prefer
-thin noodles.
-Thin noodles!
OH, NO!
No!
Thin noodles.
Thin noodles!
You're done.
…THAT WAS SO HARSH…
Must he just eat what he's given?
-What now?
-Chef's choice.
He's unable to choose.
It was chef's choice.
-He has to eat what he's given.
-You're right.
Why are you glaring at me?
I didn't say I didn't like it.
THE FRIDGE OWNER DOESN'T
CHECKS FOR TIME
He's kneading it again?
-Wait, really?
-Are you serious?
-Don't do it.
-It's okay.
-You don't have time.
-Come on.
-Don't do it.
-He's determined. And mad.
You're making it again?
-He's making thin noodles now.
-You're doing it over?
The OCC is mad.
-Really?
-The OCC is mad.
-The grandpa never yields.
-Yes, he's stubborn.
The stubborn grandpa.
It has too much flour.
-Can he fix that right away?
-No time, but he tries again.
-Wait, why?
-Are you serious?
Eight minutes left.
I mean, Seok-jin said
he liked thin noodles.
-We didn't say it.
-True.
IF THAT'S WHAT THE GUEST WANTS!
PUSHING
Made to order.
If he succeeds, it'll be huge.
He looks mad.
-He seems angry.
-You know what?
I guess the noodles will be quite chewy.
You've kneaded it a lot.
Yes, the gluten must be in action.
He's making thinner noodles.
It'd be great if someone could hold this.
He wants someone to hold it.
-Is it ready? It is.
-They're thin.
AS THIN AS THREAD
Is that what you wanted?
-Yes, it looks perfect.
-He says yes.
That's more like it. He actually did it.
That's what he wanted.
Yes, that's what I'm talking about.
DON'T TEASE ME BECAUSE I'M OLD
WE WON'T♥
That was so cool.
That's what old dudes are like.
They may grumble, but they'll do it.
-Yes.
He's like, "Is this what you want?"
He's such a grown man.
Excuse me.
Aren't the noodles a bit too thin?
No, those are fine.
-Make them thicker.
-Those are way too thin.
-Should I stop? Aren't they too thin?
-Yes.
They seem too thin.
-He wants something in the middle.
-They're too thin.
-No.
-You make it yourself, then!
THE OLD DUDE'S ANGRY…
4. CUT THE BOILED EGGS IN HALF
AND MARINATE IN SEASONED SOY SAUCE
WHAT'S EUN-YEONG UP TO?
PULLING OUT THE SHRIMP BALLS!
BOILED, DEEP-FRIED
KNIFE-CUT NOODLES
BEGINS TO COOK THE NOODLES
She put the noodles in already.
WHAT ABOUT THE SHRIMP BROTH?
BLENDING EVERYTHING IN A BLENDER
Is that the soup, Eun-yeong?
-It's reddish.
-The soup's ready?
Yes, it's the broth.
She's really fast.
She finished making the soup
while Hyun-suk was acting stubborn.
I just blended the soup for richness
-to save time.
-Right. Tomatoes.
-She added tomatoes.
-She did.
And some more seasoning. Oyster sauce.
That soup looks so good.
You don't have much time.
You have 5 minutes and 30 seconds,
but I don't see the soup.
Scallions.
The noodles are too thin.
HE'LL END UP TAKING A BLOW SOON…
He has to cook them too.
-Those noodles…
-They only take three minutes, though.
…don't take much to cook.
Sung-ju, why don't you go to the kitchen
and talk about the noodles some more?
All right.
Let me go check.
I'm looking forward to these dishes.
Hyun-suk's soup isn't ready yet.
Eun-yeong's soup is ready
with some tomatoes.
This soup is everything
for this soup round.
The soup for a grown man,
made by Eun-yeong.
Is it OldSoupSoup?
It's a bit spicy…
Huh?
WHAT IS IT?
It can use a little more kick.
-I'll add Cheongyang pepper.
-You will?
Yes.
What's with that facial expression?
Because old dudes love spicy food.
THE CHEEKY GIRL YOU CAN'T HATE
Gosh, I felt bad for asking.
Anyway, it still lacks
some depth in the flavor.
-Not enough depth.
-I still have time.
TOMATO SAUCE
CHEONGYANG PEPPER
ADDING UMAMI AND A SPICY KICK
IS HE OPENING IT?
Can you open it?
-Let me try the soup.
-It opens?
How did it happen right away?
It's a low-pressure cooker.
Something's out. What's this?
Hyun-suk's soup is ready too.
Whoa. In a pressure cooker?
-There are lots of ingredients in here.
-That's a lot.
That's pork.
Throw it in. Yes, throw it inside.
Chashu. Pork slices.
-It already looks so good.
-Look at that.
The noodles.
You need to cook the noodles.
You have three minutes left now.
-Hyun-suk cooks the noodles.
-They might stick to each other.
Let me try the soup.
He cooked it in a pressure cooker.
The soup.
SLURP
Does it taste like
you won't tease him for being old?
AMAZED!
It's so good!
REALLY?
That's what Hyun-suk does!
I love it, Hyun-suk!
-I love it!
-It's that good?
It's the kind of soup that old dudes love.
THE OLD DUDE GETS EXCITED
How did you add such depth to the soup?
You'll have to try
a little harder, Eun-yeong.
This soup tastes so deep.
So he is an old dude, after all.
He really is.
Are you using noodles too?
Yes, I have noodles.
Those look curly.
EUN-YEONG'S NOODLES ARE ALMOST DONE
You should cook your noodles.
-Did you stir the noodles?
-The noodles.
BOILING
It's boiling over!
The noodles are boiling over!
-It must be hot!
-Okay.
-Give me a strainer.
-What?
A DEPENDABLE HELP TODAY
The noodles are cooked,
and he uses a strainer.
-They're like actual ramen noodles.
-It seems so.
They're using
two distinct types of noodles.
They're using two different noodles.
-They look like ramen noodles.
-They look great.
Do they?
-It looks like a bowl of ramen.
-And the eggs? Whoa!
This is insane.
It looks so crazy.
SCALLIONS
Are you using all the noodles?
Are these it? No.
No, these aren't it.
I wanted to try the noodles.
-Hyun-suk's noodles.
-He didn't even look.
SLURP
Do the noodles taste rich,
living up to his years of experience?
The noodles are insane.
They're insane?
WHAT ABOUT THE BROTH?
They're so chewy.
He's keeping it warm.
INTO A THERMAL BOTTLE
No way, Hyun-suk.
And now…
He's done!
He's done! You surprised me.
He rings the bell in anger.
-Really?
-He has the soup in a thermal bottle.
He can pour it right before he eats.
-Eun-yeong.
-Because the noodles get soggy.
So he can pour it in?
A CONSIDERATE WAY OF SERVING NOODLES
Let me try Eun-yeong's noodles.
Eun-yeong's noodles.
-Does it taste like an old dude's noodles?
-It looks good.
DROPS THE NOODLE
It's like a magic trick.
-The paper tapes?
-But reversed.
Eun-yeong's noodles are so good too.
MAYBE HE'S JUST HUNGRY…
Old man, come and hold this.
-Old man.
-Me?
-No, old man.
-Old man.
-Hurry up. Hold this.
-What?
-Hold this and get it out.
-Okay.
It's too hot.
Twenty seconds remain.
-Hyun-suk is done.
-It's hot.
-The old Daddy Long Legs.
-Where do you want them?
-In here, old man.
-That's Hyun-suk!
SERVING THE NOODLES
THANKS TO THE OLD DADDY LONG LEGS
-What's that?
-He didn't complain,
-…but did as she asked.
-What do you need?
LASTLY, THE SOUP!
You don't have much time! Six.
-And this one.
-Five. Four. Three.
Two. One.
She's done. Eun-yeong is done too.
MOVED
-That was amazing.
-That was just…
Both dishes look so good.
Those look so good.
My hands are cold.
See? It wasn't just me.
-What's wrong?
-I wanted to pour the oil, but I couldn't.
I forgot to use the oil.
-Should I ask the old guy?
-Ask him for permission.
I wanted to add this but couldn't.
GO AHEAD AND DO IT…
GETS HIS PERMISSION AND ADDS THE OIL
PIPING HOT SOUP DISHES ARE ON THEIR WAY!
This is a neck-and-neck round.
-The soups were amazing.
-I believe you.
SNIFF
They look so good.
They were.
Both noodle and soup dishes
were made ready for Seok-jin.
AMAZED
THEY LOOK LIKE SOMETHING
A GROWN MAN WOULD LOVE
After I had a taste, I thought,
"Seok-jin is a lucky guy."
Please try Hyun-suk's dish first,
Don't Shrimp Me Because I'm Old.
RICH SHRIMPY SOUP
WITH FRESHLY MADE NOODLES TO HIS LIKING
SEASONED EGG
THIN FRESH NOODLES
SEASONED BOILED PORK
CHEF CHOI HYUN-SUK'S
DON'T SHRIMP ME BECAUSE I'M OLD
-The noodles look so good.
-He served the soup on the side.
LURKING…
What brings you here?
I wanted to provide the best service.
And you do not have to mind
that I remade thin noodles
after making thick ones
just because you like it this way.
THE PATRONIZING OLD DUDE
He reminds him of that again.
Was it two minutes?
He finished two minutes early.
In the end, it's great
that we mentioned it.
You try doing that up there.
Next time,
if you want to change it on the spot,
you make them.
THE OLD DUDE HOLDS GRUDGES
I didn't say it. It was Seok-jin.
GASP!
Whoa!
THICK
It's so rich.
-It looks so rich.
-Can you smell it?
How did he do that?
Will this go into your photo album?
Of course.
TAKING A VIDEO TO SHOW THE SOUP'S TEXTURE
Whoa, it's really…
I should've taken pictures
of my dishes too.
Why didn't I think of that?
REGRETS
He scoops some soup
-to check the texture.
-I'll try it now.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Now, the man who lives for noodles.
SLURP
Man.
AMAZED BY THE RICH SOUP
When the soup is clear and runny,
it tends to lack depth.
So if you cook the soup
with ramyeon noodles, it makes it thick.
Then the soup remains
on your tongue for longer
while having a deeper taste.
It'll probably add the texture
of what we consider ramen soup.
The shrimp ramen
you can only eat in Hokkaido.
The place with an hour and a half's wait
even at midnight.
I wonder what it's like.
-What is it like?
-Man.
I just saw him make the noodles
with my own two eyes,
-but it's totally…
-Right?
THE NOODLES CAPTURED HIS APPETITE
We didn't switch it out
with something else.
-Let me try the chashu.
-Sure.
Dip it in the soup before you eat it.
-It's also seasoned.
-It is.
He boiled it with kelp seasoning
and a bunch of dried shrimp,
-so it's seasoned.
-After that,
I coated it with seasoned soy sauce
and seared it.
That sounds so good.
Back to the soup.
SAVORING
ASTONISHED
Can you feel it
lingering on your tongue?
-What's it like?
-He couldn't eat it because of the wait.
One spoonful of soup
tastes like a stash of shrimp.
WOW
I see.
It tastes like
concentrated shrimp broth.
-It's a wonder.
-It is?
Was it called bisque? It tastes like
something that requires lots of work.
But he created this flavor
in such a short while.
But that's…
HE CAN'T STOP EATING
You can have more later.
He remade the noodles so it's thinner.
Do you prefer these thin noodles?
You know, now that I've had
these thin noodles,
I think I get what he intended
with the thick ones.
-Oh, what a shame.
-You should've stuck with it.
THIN NOODLES, RED RED
What can you do? That's the final dish.
What if you lose because of us?
-That's not our fault.
-Why not?
He was the one easily convinced.
PISSED OFF…
-He didn't ask him to change it.
-No.
He just said it.
He should've had some backbone
and stuck with it.
You should've kept it going.
Why would you change it?
-You always do what you intend to.
-Yes, I stick with it.
-Grow a spine.
-Poong.
SENSES A THREAT
-He wants you.
-Kim Poong.
After the shoot…
LOOKS AWAY
I'm busy.
Wait in the fourth dressing room.
LOL
I worked so hard on the noodles,
so please have another spoonful
of the soup.
He wants to lock him up in his soup.
CAN HE REALLY LOCK HIM UP?
One last sip.
-"Lock him up"?
-Lock him up.
Next, Eun-yeong's dish, OldSoupSoup.
HONG KONG-STYLE SHRIMP NOODLE SOUP
PERFECT FOR THE OLD DUDE'S APPETITE
CHEF PARK EUN-YEONG'S OLDSOUPSOUP
It looks fancy.
-This looks crazy too.
-She made fish balls.
You can tell that it's Hong Kong-style.
Hong Kong-style shrimp noodle soup
usually needs fresh shrimp
with their heads intact,
but you didn't have any,
so I made one to look like it.
She made a shrimp.
She made it with the head and tail,
with the meat in the middle.
AGAIN, THE SOUP FIRST
The two dishes are completely different.
Shrimp noodles and ramen.
Shrimp noodle soup.
Man.
A NECK-AND-NECK BATTLE
-It must be refreshing with the tomatoes.
-It's a close fight.
And she made it a little spicy.
Eun-yeong's soup dishes are to die for.
THE SOUPS ARE EQUALLY GOOD
They cooked with the same ingredients,
but they're so different.
The shrimp ball.
-The shrimp ball.
-That's another kick.
I'll have to try another one.
NERVOUS
These are the same, right?
Yes, but that one is deep-fried.
The others are boiled.
That's a deep-fried one.
-Even better.
-She made those
and set herself apart from Chef Hyun-suk.
I can taste the oil in here.
-The knife-cut noodles.
-They seemed unique and long.
He had those.
-Yes.
-And curly.
SLURP
HIS MOUTH IS FULL OF NOODLES
-Gosh.
-Whoa.
ONE WITH THE NOODLES
Knife-cut noodles pull in the soup
as you pick them up to eat.
-Yes.
-It adds more flavors.
They didn't look sleek. They had bumps.
-It had a charm when you bit on it.
-Yes.
CURIOUS
Wait.
What is this scent
that reminds me of Chinese cuisine?
The noodles came with oil,
so I added that.
CHINESE-STYLE SPICY LEVEL UP
WITH FLAVORED CHILI OIL
-It has that numbing mala flavor.
-Like prickly ash.
Like in malatang.
It must be chili oil.
He's in Hong Kong.
-I'm definitely in Hong Kong.
-And the fish ball.
Hyun-suk's dish didn't have those.
-These noodles have their own charm.
-Right?
So the first noodles were too thin.
The first noodles were too thin.
I get why he wanted the noodles thick.
THE FINISHING BLOW
-No!
-You should've stuck with it.
-What now?
-It's the thickness of the noodles.
My tummy hurts. Please excuse me.
Don't forget.
We were to make a soup dish, not noodles.
A soup dish.
At any rate,
if something goes wrong today,
many will get hurt.
IT'S AN EMERGENCY
-We have to run quickly.
-I have to run.
Let me get ready to run.
Come to Break Room Four.
What break room?
This soup was rich and velvety,
whereas this one
-made me feel refreshed.
-A refreshing touch.
It felt refreshing
all the way up to my brain.
When I get hungry at night,
I'd want to eat
something hearty like this.
But after having a drink the night before,
I'd want this as my hangover cure
to get refreshed as I sweat it out.
-A hangover cure?
-Yes.
Which soup appealed more
to Seok-jin, the grown man?
Which one was more captivating?
Yeo-jeong, you look so happy
as you look at him.
-I was wondering if I could get a bite.
-Of course.
Another bowl each, please.
It must be tough to choose.
-It's almost painful.
-Right?
What now?
-It's soup for a grown man.
-Grown Man's Soup.
-Yes.
-Oh, no.
THE SOUP IS HERE
That soup was so good.
My gosh. The soup.
He couldn't make more noodles.
SMELLS IT FIRST
He served just the soup for Yeo-jeong.
-And some meat.
-And meat?
I'll try this one.
-That's Chef Hyun-suk's dish.
-Thank you.
Don't Shrimp Me Because I'm Old.
GASP!
CHUCKLE
A flavor that makes you laugh.
He made this in ten minutes, right?
-Exactly.
-Right? Ten minutes or so.
What on earth is going on?
Chef & My Fridge.
IT HAPPENS ON THIS SHOW
-This is such a wonder.
-She can compare it with Eun-yeong's.
Hong Kong-style shrimp noodle soup,
OldSoupSoup.
Wow!
Your review was perfect.
-Day and night.
-Night.
It's so good.
I'm not so good with spicy food,
but this is just hot enough.
-Yes, it wasn't too spicy.
-My gosh.
YUM
-It must be tough.
-It is.
It's so good.
-Is it that good?
-Yes.
What will you do now?
-It must be tough to choose.
-I'm stressing out.
My mind
keeps changing every second.
UNPREDICTABLE
DOESN'T CARE AND TRIES THE PORK
She tries both soups at the same time.
She jumps from this soup to that soup.
I haven't had meat for a while,
and it's so good.
-Is the pork good?
-So good.
You can see that Seok-jin
is the only one aging by the minute.
-Sorry.
-This is how you grow up.
The OCC.
You mature this way.
Press one for Eun-yeong
and two for Hyun-suk.
Please make your decision
and press the button!
Before I do that,
-let me have them one last time.
-One last time.
-To leave no regrets.
-It's hard.
Leaving no regrets.
What he wanted was a man's soup.
He should try them again.
It's not easy.
EUN-YEONG'S SOUP
I shouldn't have done that.
It's more confusing.
-Oh, no.
-He's only getting confused.
STILL ADDICTED TO THE SOUPS
Press one for Eun-yeong
and two for Hyun-suk.
Press the button!
PRESS
-I did.
-He did.
How did you choose?
Grown Man's Soup.
Who did he choose?
Let's find out who Seok-jin chose.
Show us!
Hyun-suk's thick and rich soup
that's perfect for the night
versus Eun-yeong's refreshingly spicy soup
that's great for the day.
Ha Seok-jin, the grown man.
Which one did he choose?
Let's find out.
-Which one?
-Who is it?
Whose soup did you like better?
Which one?
CHOI HYUN-SUK WINS
DON'T SHRIMP ME BECAUSE I'M OLD WINS
It was Hyun-suk.
FLUTTER
-What a relief.
-Hyun-suk.
THE GROWN MAN'S PERFORMANCE
That's the Black Mantis of Geumho-dong.
-The White Mantis.
-The praying mantis.
Oh, gosh.
YOU MUST BE QUITE HAPPY
When it came to the overall quality,
Chef Eun-yeong's dish had
a great balance between
the noodles' texture and the soup.
So I thought the overall quality
of the dish was higher.
But when I considered just the soup,
-I personally prefer something rich.
-His preference.
So if I were to only consider
the "soup" factor, I liked this better.
I didn't mention this
in case it affects his decision,
but I wanted to move in with him.
-It was that good?
-Yes.
I wanted to live with him
to eat that soup forever.
Was that why you hugged him?
Yes, that was why.
You know I've never done that before.
As a ramen fan,
I'm very pleased that I made him
a dish that he has yet to try.
Above all, all of you.
WHAT ABOUT US?
Seok-jin saved you
from the brink of death.
WHAT A RELIEF
PHEW
Come on, Jung-hwan.
-The green room almost got shut down.
-Almost got shut down?
Thank you, Seok-jin.
-That's his ninth win. Congratulations.
-Congratulations!
Congratulations, Hyun-suk.
It was so good.
Congrats, Hyun-suk.
AFTER THE FIRST COOK-OFF
Wasn't it difficult?
-It was, and they were both so good.
-They were so good.
-Let me try the soup.
-It's so good.
IS IT REALLY THAT GOOD?
YUM
-Man.
-Right?
It's really rich.
Min-hyeong.
SUMMONS HER MANAGER THIS WEEK AS WELL
You have to try this one.
It's insane.
DRINKING THE SOUP
It tastes like crab soup.
Try this too.
It'll knock you out.
SLURP
Isn't it really good?
-How did he do this in 15 minutes?
-Exactly.
He actually did it in ten.
He used a pressure cooker…
SLURP
In the end, only Chef Nam-no
and Cho Yeo-jeong stayed behind to eat.
The second round of cook-off
played with Seok-jin's ingredients.
The problematic canine, Chef Sam Kim,
versus the problematic sujebi,
Chef Kwon Sung-jun.
I received a scandalous tip.
-What is it?
-It's kind of awkward.
Sung-jun refused to cook
unless we shared this news
-with everyone.
-What is it?
He made that announcement,
-so we share this reluctantly.
-Who does he think he is?
"Chef Sung-jun,
you've been doing great lately,
with 7 wins and 1 loss after 8 games."
-Whoa.
-He wanted us to point that out.
LOL
He seems so pathetic.
Are we good now?
-Yes, we're good.
-Excellent.
He's been on a roll lately,
with 7 wins, 1 loss over 8 games.
He says there's a secret
to this increase in the win rate.
Is there a secret?
I began my full-scale hunt
for the stars this year,
and it wasn't so bad.
So I want to keep going
and reach first place in the end.
-I see.
-How cool. Like how he won CCW.
So you forgot how to lose?
How do you lose?
I'm not like that, am I?
You were exactly like him.
-I was?
-Yes, you used to be like that.
He's who you were ten years ago.
Chef Nam-no hasn't won
too many stars lately.
Is there anything
you'd like to share with him?
Well, there is a secret I hold to.
But it's not something he can copy anyway.
SMUG LEVEL
-He must be pissed.
-I don't want to know anyway!
-You never know when you'll fight him.
-Right.
I'll destroy him.
It'll be funny if you lose today.
-Oh, no.
-Chef Sam.
-I want you to win against him.
-Yes, he's been a nuisance.
Can you please win against him?
I'll do my best.
Show your canine today.
CANINES, PEEK-A-BOO
A BIG SMILE
THE GOOD GUY DOES AS HE'S ASKED
That was so random.
OFFICIALLY A FAN
That was lovely.
-That smile.
-That was nice.
Sung-jun said this too.
We recorded another remark.
"These days, Chef Sam
-seems to have become my fan."
-What?
-What do you mean?
-What does this mean?
He's not the type
who strikes up a conversation first
because he's introverted.
But recently, the way he looks at me
has changed a little.
I see. How so?
He finds me endearing.
-He does?
-Yes.
I think he's studying me like a fan.
-Maybe he was dumbfounded.
-He has fallen.
-I think he fell for my charm.
-He fell for your charm.
It's not easy to leave.
I see. Sure.
-Is it true?
-Is that so, Sam?
-He's right.
-Why?
OH MY
When we first met,
I thought, "Who the heck is this guy?"
He said it nicely.
-I was like, "Who is that punk?"
-Me too.
-Everyone had that thought.
-But I caught on to his charm,
and one day,
I realized that I could predict
his psychological state
by looking at him
and listening to his words.
-I see.
-So it's fun.
He's having fun.
-Look at him now.
-What's on his mind?
What does that face mean?
That was appalling.
He seems quite nervous.
-Despite what he said?
-Yes.
-So he's nervous.
-He doesn't want to lose to Sam.
-He got me.
-Does he get smug when he's nervous?
That's his coping mechanism.
-Yes.
-You were bluffing.
It's been a while
since we've had the Italian derby.
Seok-jin will be playing
an Italian chef in his upcoming project,
so he'll probably keep a keen eye
on the way you two cook.
Will they get extra points
for sharing some skills you can use?
If there's something I can pick up.
-They get extra points?
-Yes.
I'm sure it'll be very helpful for him.
CHEF SAM'S INGREDIENTS:
STRIP LOIN, PORK BELLY, BEEF BRISKET
SCALLION, MUSHROOM CREAM SAUCE,
VEGGIE BROTH, CILANTRO, AND MORE
The dish I prepared today is
Beef WellingNull.
-Beef WellingNull?
-WellingNull?
-Null?
No?
Beef Wellington is made
by wrapping beef with ham.
Instead of ham,
-I'll use beef brisket instead.
-That's new.
So I'll use every single meat he has
and make beef Wellington,
while bringing out the Western flavors.
Why is it WellingNull?
-I'll be emptying out his fridge.
-His fridge.
-Nullifying.
-I get it.
-He'll empty it.
-He'll empty it for me.
CHEF SUNG-JUN'S INGREDIENTS:
PORK BELLY, PORK BELLY END CUT, STRIP LOIN
BEEF TONGUE, OYSTER SAUCE, SOY SAUCE,
HOT SAUCE, WHITE BALSAMIC, AND MORE
What I'll make today is called
Mantecare on the Menu.
-I see.
-Mantecare on the Menu.
Not Love on the Menu,
but Mantecare on the Menu.
Mantecare is an Italian word
that means "to mix."
-So you mix your food by shaking the wok.
-And quickly too.
I'll show you that.
I'm going to make pasta
in the style of mazesoba.
That sounds good.
-But it's meat…
-You had lots of meat,
-…so I plan to use everything.
-Everything.
I'll grind the meat
and make a sauce similar to ragu
and add a variety of toppings.
Also, it only took me three minutes
to make fresh pasta last time.
SMUG
So today, within 2 minutes and 30 seconds,
-I'll make it happen.
-You're making fresh pasta?
Also, there's a Japanese dish
which you make with leftover meat
called menchi katsu, ground meat cutlet,
made with ground meat
shaped into a ball, then deep-fried.
So I'll make that as well,
with a bit of an Italian kick.
Italian meets Japanese.
Can Seok-jin pick up
on that skill, mantecare,
by watching you cook?
It's not just mantecare.
You'll have to easily make
fresh pasta within two, three minutes
to call yourself an Italian chef.
He's quite nervous right now.
IN A NERVOUS STATE
He's analyzing him.
-My heart is racing.
-An interpreter.
And now,
let us begin their cook-off.
This is a meat round,
titled Problematic Meat.
The man who forgot how to lose.
The sujebi of ambition,
Chef Kwon Sung-jun.
I'LL PICK THAT UP!
He's here to give him a special lecture
on how to lose the cook-off.
The canine of ambition, Chef Sam Kim.
"The canine of ambition"?
Who'll rise as the winner
after this Italian derby?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
Let's go!
SUJEBI VS. CANINE
-They're using meat.
-Is that pork belly?
They're both prepping meat.
1. ROAST SEASONED PORK BELLY IN THE OVEN
Why is the oven off?
-Why is it off?
-What?
-What? Who turned off the oven?
-Emergency.
-Wait.
-The oven?
-Who is it?
-The oven was off.
IT WASN'T ME
Maybe Chef Canine.
Who turned off the oven?
I'm prepping strip loin right now.
I'm going to mix
beef with a bit of pork belly.
-Who did it?
-It wasn't me.
Borrow the one on the right.
It's okay.
You can use it.
You can use Sam's oven, right?
He's grinding beef right now.
-Emergency.
-He's using ground meat.
OFF TO A SHAKY START
They're both grinding something.
-Is that for the pasta sauce?
-Yes.
I'm grinding the meat first.
BUT HE OVERCOMES IT BRAVELY!
What's he doing?
-The dough?
-Yes, to make beef Wellington.
-To wrap the beef?
-The flour dough.
Did you add eggs? Or butter?
He added melted butter.
GROUND MEAT & PIE DOUGH
Sam ground two different ingredients.
First, the melted butter…
He's seasoning the meat.
TAP TAP TAP!
What he's doing
to season the meat is correct.
You always start with ground pepper.
Always start with the coarser ingredient.
-I see.
-I'm a chef, so when I watch dramas,
wrong details get on my nerves.
PORK BELLY END CUT, STRIP LOIN
BEEF TONGUE (FOR BULGOGI)
WATCH CLOSELY!
-Whoa.
-Yes.
Look at him chop.
COOK LIKE A CHEF
LESSON 3: KEEP YOUR HEAD AT 45°
That's Sung-jun.
He's been on a roll lately.
-He's been doing great lately.
-Yes.
He's chopping an onion too.
Don't let him win!
Look at Sam go.
That's how Italian chefs chop.
-He's good.
-Yes, that's it.
A GREAT CHANCE TO OBSERVE!
It sounds so rhythmical.
OLIVE OIL, GARLIC
SCALLIONS
2. COOK ONION, GARLIC, SCALLION
IN OLIVE OIL
SUNG-JUN'S TAKE ON THE TOPIC
He'll make the sauce similar to ragu
and serve it like mixed noodles.
GROUND THE PROBLEMATIC MEAT
AND USE IT AS SAUCE!
What's he adding? Garlic?
GASP
That was a lot of salt.
Didn't you pour in too much salt?
No, it needs this much.
It needs this much.
-Did you use garlic, Sung-jun?
-Garlic.
-Garlic, ginger, and onion.
-And ginger?
-Their processes are similar.
-They're both using onion and meat.
-The pans look similar.
A similar process.
White balsamic vinegar.
-Balsamic vinegar?
It adds sourness to the pasta.
That too, but it's also sweet.
That's a delicious sauce.
-I see.
-White balsamic vinegar.
-White balsamic.
-Yes.
SAM'S TAKE ON THE TOPIC!
-That looks good.
-That looks delicious.
I want a bite of that meat.
Keep it up, Sam.
-That must be good meat.
-It is.
He couldn't eat it alone,
so he thought it was such a waste.
-I was afraid of the security guard.
-Yes, of course.
MUSHROOM CREAM SAUCE
VEGGIE BROTH
3. COOK GROUND BEEF, SAUCE, BROTH
MAKING THE PASTA DOUGH!
-The dough?
-The pasta dough.
-That's fast.
-You're using your hand?
He's kneading with his hand.
-And not a blender?
-Not a blender.
-The pasta dough?
-Yes.
Is Sam making noodles too?
Wellington's… WellingNull's wrap.
Why are you using your hands?
Italian chefs
aren't allowed to use machines.
REALLY?
You must do everything by hand.
-But Hyun-suk used a tool.
-He did.
He's not an Italian chef?
He's a chef.
-Whoa, already?
-It's already coming out.
-It's rather yellow.
-Take your time. It's okay.
Isn't that a tool?
What's that, then? Your palms?
-Do you consider that your hand?
-Answer him.
He never answers if it's to his detriment.
Wait a minute. It doesn't seem so smooth.
Wait a second. Is that okay?
He's like me in the last episode.
Should I hold it?
He has a minute to finish up.
A minute until the time he promised.
-A minute?
-Yes.
I only need 30 seconds.
He kept running it through,
so it must be chewy.
It works well now.
IT'S COMING OUT!
Done.
-You're done already?
-I'm done.
He did it 30 seconds faster.
It took him two minutes.
Two minutes? How did I do it so quickly?
Seok-jin, is it thin enough?
UM
They look fine.
Thicker pasta may be better.
Aren't they too thin?
They aren't. Not at all.
CHECKING FOR TIME
CREAM AND MEAT MIXTURE
4. DRAIN OVER A STRAINER
THE BROTH WILL TURN INTO SAUCE!
NEXT, FLATTEN THE DOUGH THINLY
What's Sam up to?
Me? I'll wrap this now.
Mustard?
Mustard.
-He's using mustard.
-The one he asked you to use.
It should be in the oven already.
-Yes, the Wellington.
-You have no time.
Eight minutes.
It's okay.
TRUFFLE-FLAVORED MUSTARD
He topped the beef brisket
with strip loin.
You're right.
CREAM AND MEAT MIXTURE
-It's quite thick.
-Does he have enough time?
Why don't you sear it first?
No. It's okay.
Will it get fully cooked?
He cooked the strip loin
in case it doesn't.
-I see.
-And beef brisket cooks quickly.
He's cooking it in a pan first.
Okay.
-He's cooking it first.
-Eight minutes left.
Can you ground the sesame seeds?
-This one?
-Sesame seeds.
He's grinding the bread
from Seok-jin's sister.
-Really?
-The German bread.
He's using that bread. No way.
As breadcrumbs, probably.
As breadcrumbs. Yes.
GROUND BEEF TONGUE AND ONION
SOY SAUCE, OYSTER SAUCE, MILK
Is that milk? Did you add milk?
For ground beef cutlets.
People do this in Italy
to make the meat tenderer.
It's the Italian method.
I don't think you added enough.
That was a tiny dash.
-Did he not have enough?
-Was it not enough?
No, not too much. Less is more.
He's really fast.
By less, do you mean milk?
Sure.
Great question.
And a good answer.
That makes sense.
The meat is coming undone.
Poong, look at him.
His Wellington is falling apart.
Beef brisket is coming undone!
That can't happen
when you make a Wellington!
-It's coming undone!
-It's okay.
Is he serious?
You should do it over.
You're awful, Hyun-suk.
Why did you put him up for it?
He just made Poong do that.
I thought he was telling him to help.
Why did you make me do it?
You're mean.
You two are the same.
You're both mean.
They're so funny.
Things are heating up.
Sung-jun is making another batter.
He'll dip the cutlet in that
before the breadcrumbs.
The batter.
He'll dip the meat in that first.
And not just breadcrumbs?
Is that the recipe?
That's the way to do it.
For ground beef cutlets?
COOK LIKE A CHEF
LESSON 4: BIG AND QUICK ACTION!
Do you see this, Jee Seok-jin?
He's Ha Seok-jin.
Wait, Jee? I meant Ha Seok-jin.
We're hearing his name often today.
FAREWELL, PIZZA, WE WON'T SEE YOU OFF
-Minus five points!
-Come on!
Ha Seok-jin!
It's an emergency.
A BIG MISS…
Where's the emergency light?
I'm sorry, Ha Seok-jin.
You have six minutes to go.
The pasta? Already?
Pasta made with eggs
will cook really quickly.
Sam put the meat on the pie dough.
That's the Wellington.
Seok-jin has his eyes on the chefs.
CHECKING FOR TIME
He has to stick it in the oven
to let the dough get cooked.
-Yes.
-Just flatten it with your hands.
Wow.
As you watch him, you'll probably realize
that the chef
who made Wellington last year
did an excellent job.
THE ORIGINAL SMUG GUY
It must've been you.
Yes, it was me.
THE SMUG CHOIMPION OF THE SHOW!
Sung-jun only picks up on those things.
The mischievous things.
-Stick it on now.
-It goes into the oven.
It went in
with only 5 minutes and 20 seconds left.
COOK LIKE A CHEF
LESSON 5: KNIFE TIP STAYS ON THE BOARD!
Five minutes and thirty seconds.
CHIVES
Sung-jun gets the pasta out.
Huh?
Don't you think the pasta is too thin?
-Is that okay?
-Should he do it over?
It'll swell up a bit.
ADD THE PASTA!
MANTECARE ON THE MENU!
Mantecare is an Italian word
that means "to mix."
SEE THIS, JEE… HA SEOK-JIN?
COOK LIKE A CHEF
LESSON 6: MANTECARE IS A MUST FOR PASTA!
Five minutes!
Jung-hwan, please report from the kitchen.
It's the first Italian derby in a while.
Sesame oil?
Nice.
Will Sam destroy Sung-jun's spirit?
-Breadcrumbs?
-Breadcrumbs.
-Sung-jun's breadcrumbs are ready.
German breadcrumbs.
-The meat mix.
-German breadcrumbs.
The meat mixture.
You have to deep-fry these, right?
Sung-jun looks focused.
-Are you leaving the pasta like this?
-Yes.
That's so cool.
-No flour, though?
-He's looking cool.
WATCH CLOSELY!
Give him a look.
LIKE THIS
Are you watching him, Jee Seok-jin?
COMEDY IS ALL ABOUT REPETITION!
AGAIN, WE APOLOGIZE,
BOTH HA SEOK-JIN AND JEE SEOK-JIN
I'm sorry!
It's time to coat them
with breadcrumbs and deep-fry.
He's coating it with breadcrumbs.
-The oil doesn't look hot enough.
-It doesn't?
It's working.
-It's high enough.
-Is it?
-Actually, it's a bit too high.
-It's too high.
DROPPING THE TEMPERATURE
Take them out and try again.
It looks fine now.
Jung-hwan, why don't you try the pasta?
Sung-jun's pasta.
-Parmesan.
-The sauce.
Does it taste like
he doesn't know how to lose?
GULP
It seems so, but…
BUT?
…why does it taste like bulgogi?
He added sesame oil.
No, it's mazesoba.
-Mazesoba?
-It's mixed pasta.
Is it supposed to be like bulgogi?
-He added sesame oil.
-It tastes like bulgogi to me.
-It's the sesame oil.
But it's good.
-He's making it in a different way.
-Okay!
AS REQUESTED, WHITE BALSAMIC VINEGAR
-I have a bad feeling about it.
-He requested that they use it.
You add rice vinegar to mazesoba, right?
-Yes.
-He's doing that.
It'll taste pretty good
with a raw egg yolk on top.
I think Sung-jun's pasta is ready.
He's plating the pasta.
-That's his pasta.
-You have 1 minute and 40 seconds.
Sung-jun's pasta is ready.
BARELY ENOUGH TIME
He's now waiting for the oven.
What's that?
It's butter.
Butter.
-What are you cooking right now?
-The sauce.
-Can you try that sauce?
-This sauce.
-The sauce.
-The canine sauce!
-The problematic sauce!
Does it taste like
he'll teach Sung-jun how to lose?
He'll definitely teach him how.
SAM KIM THE STAR INSTRUCTOR!
It's very smooth.
What did you add? Mushrooms?
I used the mushroom pasta sauce.
-It tastes so good.
-Sam uses the sauce.
-He used that?
-The Italian round.
One minute left.
It'll be tough for him to choose.
WHAT WILL COME OUT
FROM THE PROBLEMATIC OVEN?
-What's that?
-One minute left.
The seasoned pork he made.
He put that in the oven?
Is that chashu?
Is this the topping?
-Yes, it's like chashu.
-Chashu.
WHAT'S IN SAM'S OVEN?
The Wellington is ready.
Wait, you have no time. Forty seconds.
8. PULL THE WELLINGNULL OUT OF THE OVEN
AND SEAR IT WITH A TORCH
The gas won't work.
It got on the paper!
The paper makes it smoky?
EGG
Twenty seconds.
The sauce is boiling.
10. TOP PASTA WITH EGG YOLK,
SEASONED ROASTED SEAWEED, AND CILANTRO
Sesame seeds.
-Sesame seeds.
-Sprinkle it on top.
GROUND SESAME SEED
What about this?
I have to get it out.
-Nine. Eight.
-Seven. Six.
Ten seconds!
PLATING THE DISH
WITH ONLY 10 SECONDS LEFT!
SMOOTH CREAM SAUCE!
SEA URCHIN ROE
WOBBLY
-Ring it first.
-The bell!
Ring the bell first!
-Ring it first.
-The bell!
TIME'S UP!
-Sam finishes first.
-Sam finishes.
-Sam's done.
-He topped it with sea urchin roe?
-He topped it with sea urchin roe.
-He did.
-Sung-jun is done too.
-He's done.
SUNG-JUN FINISHES MANTECARE ON THE MENU
Wow.
DISHES WITH A GREEN TOUCH
They both worked on
timely dishes this time.
It's impossible in 15 minutes.
These meat dishes.
It's crazy.
And now, both dishes were made
to fill Seok-jin's order.
The 15 minutes went by so quickly.
You're playing an Italian chef,
so we thought you'd have
a lot of to learn in this round.
At first, they offered to teach you,
but one of them
even called you Jee Seok-jin.
He didn't even show you how to mantecare.
Also, there is a bit of a problem
-that I wish to pose.
-What is it?
Before the round started,
Sung-jun went to the oven and said,
"Who turned off the oven?"
THE OVEN WAS TURNED OFF
-Yes.
-Did you see that?
It reminded me of something else.
-What is it?
-What?
Once before, Chef Ho-young
also suffered because
someone had turned off the fridge.
I think the freezer's broken.
THE DAY WHEN HE MADE BINGO MANGSU
Yes, right.
-The day he made bingo mangsu.
-Wait, no.
And oddly, his opponent that day
was also Sam Kim.
-Sam Kim.
-What?
Oh, my gosh!
IS THIS A COINCIDENCE?
Is it just me?
-My gosh.
-Gosh.
-When the freezer went out,
-Really?
…he was playing against Sam.
Was that his strategy?
I hoped it wouldn't be.
As soon as I got here today,
he asked me for the circuit box.
Did he really?
Yes, I wondered why he wanted to know.
I'm getting chills.
He asked me too.
"Do you think I can
cut the wire with my canine?"
TOO MUCH…
I'm dead serious.
Wow.
Was that how you were using your canine?
-I see.
-Who turned it off?
Was this Sam's grand plan? Nobody knows.
If he wins again today,
this is bound to happen often.
Careful, everyone. Watch out.
Now, Sam finished first.
Beef WellingNull.
BEEF WELLINGNULL
TO MAKE THE MEAT IN THE FRIDGE NULL
CHEF SAM KIM'S BEEF WELLINGNULL
SMELLS IT FIRST
It smells so good.
-Does it?
-First of all,
-see how well the meat is cooked.
-I'll cut it.
-Wow.
-It must be nicely cooked.
CUTTING
ALL EYES ON THE DISH
He'll see meat inside.
IS THIS COOKED?
-It's cooked.
-Is it cooked nicely?
When you make Wellington,
you can't have the meat well done.
It has to be a little rare.
I see.
He hasn't been cooking meat at home
after the holiday trauma.
TAKING A BIG BITE
He takes a big bite.
SOFT GAZE
WHOA
He glances at Sam for a brief moment.
Emergency.
OH, LOOK AT THIS THING
He truly is an old dude.
He stares at the food when it's delicious.
OLD DUDE STARTER PACK: STARES AT GOOD FOOD
Man.
ANOTHER BITE WHILE STARING
He savors the dish quietly.
What is it?
-What's this bouncy texture?
-The bouncy texture?
Wellington is made
with beef tenderloin wrapped with ham.
You had beef brisket,
so I used it to create a similar texture.
That's probably the bouncy texture.
Beef brisket… It must be the one here.
THIS TIME, JUST THE MEAT
Does it go well with the meat?
Yes, it does.
And the sauce has a dash of sourness,
which balances out the greasiness.
I made it with mustard,
-so it must be that.
-I guess so.
And I saw him spread it
on the pie dough too.
SLURP
-Gosh.
-Another bite.
-He wolfs it down.
-He must've wanted to eat meat badly.
Gosh. This is good.
I see. Look how happy he is.
Old dudes always look up.
OLD DUDE STARTER PACK:
LOOKS UP WHEN IMPRESSED
Either the ground or the sky.
-That was delicious.
-All right.
-So this is what it's like.
-He looks pleased.
Next, Chef Sung-jun's dish,
Mantecare on the Menu.
MIXED PASTA MADE
WITH A VARIETY OF GROUND MEAT
GROUND MEAT CUTLET WITH SEA URCHIN ROE
CHEF KWON SUNG-JUN'S MANTECARE ON THE MENU
This is Japanese-style mixed pasta.
He basically likes
everything that's ramen.
The noodles look so good.
-But it's pasta.
-It'll taste nice with that sour note.
Japanese-style mixed pasta.
Hmm?
Jung-hwan said
it tasted like bulgogi sauce.
YUM
-Cilantro?
-Cilantro.
Yes, I like that cilantro smell.
Cilantro changed the flavor
that could've been too cliché.
What do you mean by cliché?
As you said, bulgogi.
Right? It tastes like bulgogi.
It feels more like
Korean cuisine, actually.
He poured in sesame oil.
He's facing a danger.
-Emergency.
-Yes.
-Where's the light?
-It's an emergency.
Where's the light?
He gets rid of it when he cooks.
He carries it on him?
The emergency light is mine.
We should've turned it on now.
-To not let anyone else use it?
-He took it?
You were trying to make
bulgogi pasta, right?
I'm a guy who's Korean to his core, so…
ANALYZING…
He's nervous right now.
-You're so nervous.
-He's in a crisis.
Try the ground beef cutlets.
He tries to get him
to try the beef cutlets.
-I wonder if it's fully cooked.
-I don't think so.
-I doubt it.
-It's cooked.
It can't be reddish.
Is it cooked?
-It's fully cooked.
-It is?
It's fully cooked.
It continued to cook.
-I wasn't so sure before.
-Right?
-Thank goodness you rang the bell later.
-Yes, it's thanks to that.
Between the two dishes,
which one would you put
a bigger emphasis on?
It's obvious, because the topic
was Problematic Meat.
The dish that was made
to use up these problematic meats
was the beef cutlet.
That's the main dish.
I see. So the pasta goes?
I only made the pasta to show Seok-jin
my techniques.
-To teach him how to mantecare.
-As an example?
He's lying right now.
-Is that his lying face?
-That's not the case.
He claims
the beef cutlet is the main dish.
They're topped with sea urchin roe.
Will the fish roe
go well with the beef cutlets?
-Let me try another bite.
-One more bite.
-This isn't…
-I guess he's not sure yet.
He has another bite.
I guess it's somewhat…
CAREFUL…
Is it good or…
We aren't sure if that is
a positive or a negative response.
Is it the seasoning?
Did you not make it with sauce…
You're eating it yourself.
What are you doing?
He's suddenly eating it himself.
That's mine. Stop eating.
What were you checking for, Sung-jun?
Well,
he didn't say much, so I tried it.
-He's anxious.
-"Why is he so quiet?"
-It tastes good.
-"I think it's good."
Because it's not easy to make
such a tender ground beef cutlet.
-Really?
-It's nice and juicy.
It is good.
Let me ask you once more.
What's the main dish? Pasta or cutlets?
-Give him your answer.
-Choose wisely.
THINKING…
After all, I'm an Italian chef…
OF COURSE, IT'S THE PASTA
While he thinks about it,
we should let Yeo-jeong try some too.
Yeo-jeong will try the dish.
Will she also like these dishes?
He put a lot of work into the sauce.
A BIG BITE
TWO THUMBS UP
This is so good.
She says, "This is so good."
How did the pie sheet turn out so tender?
I made it as thin as possible.
-That's why it's tender.
-I see.
And the mustard he spread inside
was a really good kick.
He used truffle-flavored mustard,
so it can intensify the meat flavor.
He brought it up.
Next, Chef Sung-jun's dish.
I was curious about these noodles.
SLURP
LOL
Is it bulgogi noodles?
What do you think?
This bulgogi is delicious.
-Bulgogi is the best.
-"This bulgogi is delicious."
Eonyang bulgogi pasta.
Open up a Korean restaurant.
-I knew it.
-It's so good.
Next, ground beef cutlets
with sea urchin roe.
YUM
A CLOSER LOOK…
NERVOUS
Do you feel thirsty? Is it too dry?
It's quite tender.
It's not dry at all, but…
-What is it?
-But?
But I keep wondering
if he served it with anything else.
If I may tell you this frankly,
it's not salty enough.
Because this dish had a strong flavor,
-this tastes more bland in comparison.
-You're right.
He should've seasoned it more.
Sam, what kind of state
is Sung-jun in right now?
He has checked out.
PRETTY MUCH A MIND READER
You know Sung-jun too well.
It was about time he checked out.
NODDING…
He looks like he has given up.
All right, now. Problematic Meat.
Press one for Sung-jun
and two for Sam. Goodness.
Sung-jun's win rate had been great so far.
But he has his eyes closed right now.
It looks like he has let many things go.
You never know.
Did you choose one?
-I did.
-He did.
He even turned off
the power for Sung-jun's oven.
We might see him
on a true crime channel soon.
1. A FAMOUS CHEF
HABITUALLY TURNS OFF POWER
We'll see him in one of the episodes.
We'll investigate
what happened today after the shoot.
I need the video replay.
Problematic Meat.
Which dish did Seok-jin choose? Show us!
Sung-jun has been on a roll lately,
not knowing what the word "losing" means.
But Sam is here to tell him how to lose.
Which dish did Seok-jin choose?
What's the result for Problematic Meat?
SAM KIM WINS
CHEF SAM KIM'S BEEF WELLINGNULL WINS
It was Sam.
SAM WINS WITHOUT A TWIST!
There will be a controversy.
The thing is,
if Chef Sung-jun had finished first
and I got to try the cutlets, noodles,
and then the Wellington,
-the result would've changed drastically.
-I see.
Chef Sam's dish
left such a strong impression.
Let me ask you one last time.
Did you tamper with the oven?
I'll let you know in the next episode.
He's good.
APPROVED
We can do a back-and-forth now.
I believe we must get down
to the root of the problem.
Yes, it's frightening.
Please leave the kitchen as is.
We'll have a forensics team come by,
so don't touch anything.
Leave everything as is before you go.
Can you reinvestigate my cook-off too?
-Even Ho-young's round?
-Reinvestigate?
We will take that into consideration.
HEHE
Please put a star on Sam.
-Great job.
-Seok-jin chose Chef Sam.
That's Sam's eighth star!
Congratulations, Sam.
COMING UP: JONATHAN & PATRICIA,
BIBI & NAKYOUNG'S PREVIEW
Please welcome today's fridge owners!
The sisters, BIBI and NaKyoung,
and the siblings, Jonathan and Patricia.
-We kiss each other on the cheek.
-I can do it now.
THE TWO LOVING SISTERS
LEAVE THE SIBLINGS IN SHOCK
How loving can you be?
Sitting next to each other.
Or how you end up
rubbing on each other when you fight.
Right now, we're the most physical
we have ever been.
THE LOVING SISTERS' SPICY TWIST
You eat it all, pig!
THE SPICY SISTERS
PRESENT THEIR FRIDGE
We love spicy food so much.
Aren't these really spicy?
Do you not feel it?
Is there anything spicier?
FOR THE SISTERS WHO LOVE THE RED FLAVOR,
ALL KINDS OF RED DISHES ARE SERVED
The sexy grandpa.
Someone call 911.
That's insane.
That's going to kill you!
-I love it.
-It's too spicy.
THE SPICY SISTERS' EATING MODE
MMM
That's what I'm talking about.
It looks so good.
THE SISTERS' MUKBANG
WHICH CHEF CAPTURED THE APPETITE
OF THESE TWO SISTERS?
They seem quite unrivaled.
You have that distinct color.
-What do you mean by "distinct color"?
-We are colored, yes.
-I mean, we're all colored.
-You'll get canceled.
-It's not that.
-You'd better be careful.
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn